原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译   千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译   AlgerDestiny  Stampy  五天
翻译   A序列  马丁马丁回音山  不见  VC
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     Caroline
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
希望你有看过第一部分
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第二十集
请山寨别的节目
你们谁也不会继承到任何东西
None of you will inherit anything.
因为本来就没东西传下去
Because there isn't any.
上周新闻
辛普森一家前情提要
Previously on The Simpsons,
一位颇具魅力的新牧师来到春田镇
a charismatic new preacher came to Springfield.
你要拿我的枪吗  你可以拿
You want to hold my gun? Y-You can.
丽莎前所未有地崇拜他
And Lisa admired him like no adult man she'd ever met.
这顿早午餐已经变成爵士风味了
This brunch has turned into... a jazz brunch!
勒弗乔伊神父失去了工作
Reverend Lovejoy lost his job
并发誓要报仇
and swore revenge.
接下来是
This is...
向神父宣战
第二部
春田第一教堂
三个恶霸当男仆
好处多多
这个新牧师太赞了
This preacher is so amazing.
我很期待这场布道
I'm looking forward to this.
这是我第一次没有以大型蒙太奇的方式
This is the first time I've come to church
出现在教堂现场
when it's not part of a big montage
我的敌人们也没杀掉
of my enemies being whacked.
有人为了来教堂特意打扮了一番
Well, someone looks awfully nice for church.
你说这个
Oh, this thing?
你确定你不是被
Are you sure you aren't just attracted
我们帅哥新牧师吸引了吗
to our handsome new pastor?
傻瓜  妈咪不会被牧师吸引的
Silly. Moms aren't attracted to pastors.
这地方真拥挤
Oh, this place is so crowded.
我的腿都碰到苗浩斯老爸的腿了
My leg is touching Milhouse's dad's.
看来我们是邻膝了哈老兄
Looks like we're knee neighbors, huh, buddy?
史密瑟斯先生
Mr. Smithers.
我从没见过你不跟在伯恩斯先生后面
I don't think I've ever seen you without Mr. Burns.
伯恩斯先生在家更舒服
Oh, Mr. Burns is more comfortable at home
读着他《圣经》的各种版本
reading his copies of the scriptures.
"赐福穷人"
"Blessed be the poor"?
我现在才知道这句话
I'm just finding this out now?
谁也不准知道
No one must know.
灰常好
Exellus.
早上好
Good morning.
对那些喜欢橄榄球比赛的人来说...
For those of you interested in the Packers game...
我们不想知道
We don't want to know.
我知道你们中有些人对我还有些疑问
So, I know some of you still have some questions about me.
我算一个
I certainly do.
你愿意当我儿子的教父吗
Will you be godfather to my son?
我们还没到那步呢  梅尔
We're not there yet, Mel.
但是说真的  越来越少有人来教堂了
But, seriously, fewer and fewer people are coming to church.
人数在减少
Numbers are declining.
我也很理解
And I get it.
当你告诉别人你相信上帝
When you tell people that you believe in God,
通常他们都以为你的意思是
usually they take that to mean
你是在无声地批判他们的生活方式
that you're quietly judging their lifestyle
或是以为除你之外的所有人都会下地狱
or think everybody but you is going to Hell.
就会说教  贱人
Way to preach, bitch.
我就假装自己听到的是"阿门"
I'm gonna pretend I heard "amen."
放轻松  贱人
Oh, relax, bitch.
宗教原始的功能
The original function of religion
就是让所有人团结在一起  宗教
was to bring us together. "Religion."
宗  就像是韧带
"Ligio," like "ligament."
意思是重新联系
It means to reconnect.
在医学院可不会教这种东西
They don't teach you that at medical school.
不  教的
Yes, they do.
我在我的错误中吸取了教训
Well, I learn from my mistakes.
不熟不能生巧
Malpractice makes malperfect.
我想让我们所有人团结在一起
Well, I want to bring us all together.
不止是基督徒  还有印度教徒和佛教徒
Not just Christians but Hindus and Buddhists.
甚至是那些不信教的人
Even those that don't believe.
除我之外还有没有人
Does anyone besides me
怀念教堂之前的样子
miss church the way it was?
好吧  蟋蟀赞同
Well, the crickets agree.
我们说的是不
这座教堂已经从一个
This church has gone from a place
温暖  安静到尴尬的地方  变成了现在
of warm, awkward silence into a gooey lovefest
被你这个自恋的小子经营的网红地
run by a narcissistic kum-bah-yo-yo,
我绝对不能忍
and I will not stand for it.
你我信仰同一个上帝
You and I believe in the same God.
我只是相信  上帝爱所有人
I just believe that that God loves everyone.
你不赞同这个说法吗  内德
You don't agree with that, Ned?
先生  我们还没到直呼大名的程度呢
Sir, we are not on a first-name basis.
弗兰德斯先生
Mr. Flanders.
你何以叫我内·新福音执事·德
You may call me New Evangelical Deacon,
或者简称为内德
or Ned for short.
好的  内德
Okay, Ned, look,
上帝就是爱  有了他才让宇宙开始运行
God is the love, the "yes" that set the universe in motion.
他  或是她
He or She...
或许这一次
Maybe this time.
*或许这一次*
*Maybe this time*
*我会相信*
*I will believe it*
周日  好衣服
周日  更好的衣服
周日  最好的衣服
*或许这一次  我会祈祷*
*Maybe this time, I will pray*
*或许这一次*
*Maybe this time*
*是第一次*
*For the first time*
*我会在周日找到乐趣*
*I'll have fun on Sunday*
*他会用那淡褐色的眼睛布道*
*He will sermonize with those hazel eyes*
*我有佛祖*
*‭I've got Buddha*
*我有科学*
*I've got science*
*第三个是耶稣*
*And now Jesus makes three*
*会实现的*
*It's gonna happen*
欢迎
*不一定什么时候*
*Happen sometime*
欢迎
*或许这一次*
*Maybe this time*
救赎过程不会对外播出
*我会祈祷*
*I'll pray*
不错  孩子  还有提升的空间
Not bad, kid. Also not good.
我来给你演示一下动作
Let me show you how it's done.
一哒哒  二哒哒
And a one, and a two.
在教堂里酣睡
Sleeping in church.
有其父必有其女
Like father like daughter.
上帝只不过是恩典和传教还有宽恕的结合体
God is nothing but grace and flow and forgiveness.
如果你不这样认为的话
And if you don't think so,
我不知道怎么办  也许你应该回去
I-I don't know, maybe you should go back
再稍微深入的研读一下《圣经》
and read the Bible a little bit closer.
你是在质疑
Are you questioning a man
一个把备用《圣经》放在旅馆房间的人吗
who travels with extra Bibles to put them in hotel rooms?
你介意离开吗
Do you mind?
我肯定你的虔诚
I'm sure you're very sincere,
这就像鹦鹉只会背诵《圣经》却不解文意
but a parrot can recite the Bible and have no idea what it means.
什么  什么  什么
What? What? What?
这里不再是教堂了
This isn't church anymore.
我们要走了
We're out of here.
爸爸  牧师没说走我们就不能走
Daddy, we can't leave before the pastor says so.
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?
是你啊
You did.
你把这个叫侯默·辛普森式磨炼
You call it "Homer Simpson-ing."
别把侯默·辛普森扯进来  蠢货
Yeah, don't Homer Simpson, you jerk.
与此同时  密歇根州这边
圣买大教堂
汉堡王中王
复活节遭到除名的帅气牧师
这里就是他被开除的地方
This is where he got fired.
现在我们要开始探寻
Now we're gonna poke into
完美牧师先生的申秘过去
Mr. Perfect Pastor's pysterious past.
你刚才说的是申秘吗
Did you just say "pysterious"?
你能不能别跟我对着干
Can't you be on my side for once?
打扰一下  我们要找牧师
Excuse me, we're looking for the pastor.
我们没有牧师
Oh, we don't have pastors.
但是我们的触控向导有虚拟助手
But our touch screen directory does have a digital assistant.
您好  我是神牛  能为您做些什么
Hi, I'm Holy Cow. How can I help you?
请按住屏幕让我们获取您的指纹
Please give us your fingerprint by pressing this screen.
我们为什么来到这里  可以同性恋吗
泊车核准  根据错误程度排名的其他信仰
您什么都没点  试试吧
You haven't pressed anything. Why not?
坏的好心人  好的好心人
升天
比特币支付  每月自动扣费
我想和介于你和上帝之间的人对话
I'd like to speak to someone below God and above you.
也许你能在这里找到你想要的
Well, maybe you can find what you need in here.
爽嗨可乐
创世之初  爽翻天
谦逊
营造和平氛围
你们中有多少人受到间皮瘤的困扰
How many of you suffer from the effects of mesothelioma?
找耶稣  请拨888
Dial Jesus at ocho, ocho, ocho,
ocho, ocho, ocho, ocho.
荣耀计
请帮帮我们吧
Please help us.
这位先生是一名神职人员
This man is a fellow clergyman.
真的吗
Really?
教堂  尖顶  大门  人
Church. Steeple. Doors. People.
跟我来
Come with me.
麦克牧师  有两位客人想见您
Preacher Mac, I have a couple here to see you.
我想与您讨论一件不甚愉快的事
I'm here to discuss a matter of some unpleasantness.
你们不会是《波士顿环球报》的人吧
You're not here from The Boston Globe, are you?
逃生包
不不不不不  我也是一名牧师
No, no, no, no, no. I'm a pastor, too.
我是为了了解一位曾在这里
I'm here there's a little dirt on the collar
布道的人的丑闻来拜访您的
of a man who use to preach here
伯德·莱特
Bode Wright.
帅气牧师在复活节被罢免
他  你最好坐下听我说
Him? You better sit down.
故事不长  但我很能添油加醋
It's a short story, but I'm gonna milk it.
我想接着讲
I would go on,
可我嗓子都快讲哑了
but I'm down to my last vocal cord.
即使在牧师里
even for a pastor
我说话也够绕圈子了
I've taken way too long to make a simple point.
好了  证据在这里
Now, here's the proof.
希律王宫  塔希提岛
我天  在我的教区里有这么多单身的人
Oh, my God, so many singles in my area
您教区里想与您见面的单身人士
想见我
want to meet me.
从属无关紧要
Possessions don't matter,
金钱无关紧要  这也无关紧要
money doesn't matter, this doesn't matter.
他烧的是我所想的那个东西吗
Is he burning what I think he's burning?
我抓住他的把柄了
I've got him now.
《圣经》
丽莎·玛丽·辛普森
Lisa Marie Simpson
你在读《圣经》吗
Are you reading the Bible?
嗯  书不错  可是...
Yes, it's good, but...
我有几条标注
I have a few notes.
种族主义者  性别歧视者  对赫梯人不公平  乱伦
我从没遇到过
Yeah, well I never met a Hittite
不想向埃及扩展疆域的赫梯人
who wasn't trying to expand his empire into Egypt.
赫梯人  比迦南人还糟
Oh, Hittites... worse than the Canaanites!
现在是谁为了新来的帅气牧师这么做啊
Now who's doing it because of the handsome new pastor?
莱特牧师
Reverend Wright?
你觉得他
You think he's...
我就不遮遮掩掩的了
Oh, why pretend?
他每句话  我觉得都是在说给我听
When he speaks, I feel like he's speaking only to me.
丽莎宝贝  我担心你陷得太深
Oh, Lisa, honey, I'm worried you'll get too attached.
任何新且独特的东西在这里都不会被接受
This town has a way of rejecting what's new and different.
好的东西也是
And better.
这次不一样
Not this time.
但看看你的愿景板
But look at your vision board.
全是令人心碎的失望
It's full of nothing but crushing disappointment.
愿景板
我放弃  失败  坚持没用  你输了
连愿景板本身都这么逊
Even your vision board is a failure.
那钩子本该承担
That hook was supposed to hold
我一生失望的重量
a lifetime's worth of disappointment.
"土星汽车  退到我后面吧"
Get thee behind me, Saturn.
引自圣经原文
"撒旦  退到我后面吧"
我得小便
I need to pee.
没时间  我们急着去剥下他那身牧师的皮
No time. We've got defrocking to do.
提姆  你这个样子我从没见过
Timothy, I've never seen you like this.
也许我也可以剥下谁的衣服
Maybe I'll do some defrocking, too.
在小火车房吗
In the choo choo room?
没兴致了
Okay, mood's gone.
两杯啤酒  老谋子
Two beers, Moe.
牧师什么都不要
Nothing for the reverend.
你好  牧师
Oh, howdy there, Rev.
不能让他看到我的裸女杯
Well, can't let him see my nudie glasses.
你没必要砸碎裸女杯
You didn't have to break your nudie glasses.
你说晚了  那帮我想想
Now you tell me. Uh, remind me--
一个女的有几个胸来着
how many boobs does a woman have?
我从未说过这么多心里话
I never got so much off my chest.
我曾垂涎过邻居的割草机
So, then I coveted my neighbor's riding mower.
我骑双人自行车从不踩踏板
I never pedal when I'm on a bicycle built for two.
-侯默  -我三十岁还在"不给糖就捣乱"
- Homer... - I went trick-or-treating when I was 30.
还有  我跟马姬说去做结肠镜检查
Also, I told Marge I was going for a colonoscopy
其实是看了《猩球崛起》系列
when I actually went to a "Planet of the Apes" marathon.
包括蒂姆·波顿那部
Including the Tim Burton one.
-上帝不会在乎的  -哈利路亚
- God doesn't care. - Hallelujah!
行行好别叫了  我还要在这谋生
Please. I make my living in here.
抱歉  那我被原谅了吗
Sorry. So am I forgiven?
你是个好人  侯默·辛普森
You're a good man, Homer Simpson.
抛开你所有的善恶行为
Behind all your behavior, good and bad,
你生命中仍有自在之地
there's a still, quiet place
未被生活的蹂躏所影响
untouched by the dramas of this life
在那片净土上你是善良的
where you simply "are" goodness.
我还没说最坏的那次
Oh, you haven't heard the worst one.
我对厕纸广告上的熊妈妈
I had impure thoughts
曾有过不洁的想法
about the mother bear in the toilet paper ads.
尊敬的牧师  如果你真是的话
Reverend? If that is your real honorific.
教区居民的拜访你要迟到了
You are late for our parishioners' visit.
我准备了一整天呢
I've been preparing all day.
抱歉  我得走了
Uh, sorry. I've got to go.
侯默  这个叫弗兰德斯的有没有惹过你
Homer, does this Flanders guy ever annoy you?
偶尔吧
From time to time.
动一动  动一动
Move it, move it, move it.
好的
All right.
你哪只手按的喇叭
Which arm did the honking?
才不告诉你
I'm not telling.
请进
Come in.
先生  你要跟我挑战谈论圣经
You,sir, have challenged me on scripture.
好吧  既然你想谈的是圣经
Oh. Well, if it's scripture you want to talk,
那让我们把欢呼献给上帝
then let us make a joyful noise unto the Lord.
-没问题  -好的
-Good. -Good.
惩罚是信仰的关键
Punishment is the key to belief.
马太福音25:46
Matthew 25:46.
"这些人要往永刑里去  但..."
"They will go away to eternal punishment, but the..."
"但那些义人要往永生里去"  没错
...righteous to eternal life." Sure.
但上帝的恩典是给每个人的
But God's grace is for everyone.
约翰福音12:32
John 12:32.
"我要使众人..."
"I will draw all people..."
"...都归于我"
"...up to myself." Hmm.
那听这个  帖撒罗尼迦后书1:9
What about 2 Thessalonians 1:9?
他们将遭受永远毁灭的惩罚...
"They will suffer the punishment of eternal destruction..."
罗马书11:32
Romans 11:32.
他可以宽恕他们所有人
"He may have mercy on them all."
所有人
Them all.
圣水
创世纪3:23
Genesis 3:23.
于是耶和华把他从园中赶出去
"So the Lord banished him from the Garden."
创世纪1:31
Genesis 1:31.
上帝看到了他所创造的一切
"God saw all that He had made,
一切甚好
and it was very good."
我凉了
I'm cold, so cold.
我还穿了三件毛衣
And I'm wearing three sweaters.
春田镇第一教堂
阿罗哈  星期天
要是夏威夷人民相信上帝
Wow. This is what it would be like
场面一定就像现在这样
if they believed in God in Hawaii.
牧师  你来我家吃晚饭吧
Reverend, you come to dinner at my house!
还是改天吧
Uh, yeah, I'm gonna take a rain check.
总说改天  改天是哪天
So many checks, so little rain.
停止这场狂欢
Stop this revelry!
你是谁
Who are you?!
勒弗乔伊牧师
Reverend Lovejoy!
我刚从密歇根州回来
And I'm just back from Michigan.
你能帮我怒指他一下吗
Can you point accusingly for me?
没问题
You got it.
这个人是个异教徒
This man is a heretic.
哦不  丽莎  别
Oh, no. No, Lisa, don't.
大家等一等
Wait, wait, wait!
我们当然知道牧师他收到上帝祝福...
Surely, we know the reverend is a blessed man who...
丽莎  我做过一些坏事
Lisa, I did something bad.
说真的  能有多坏
How bad could it be? Seriously.
看看你们
Well, look at you,
终于注意我了
finally paying attention to me.
简单说一下  停车场里有辆亮着灯的
One brief announcement: there's a red Honda Civic
-红色本田思域  -他们要没耐心了
- in the parking lot with its lights on. - You're losing them.
他烧了《圣经》
He burned the Bible.
天啊
Oh, boy.
太可怕了  你们说说看
That's appalling. I mean, come on.
赞美诗可不是用来烧的  是用来纹身的
Psalms are not for burning. They're for tattoos.
所以你让我很难受
So, you know, you sicken me.
我心里的声音告诉我这不是真的
Everything in my heart tells me this isn't true!
我知道在教堂里说这话很奇怪
I know this is a weird thing to say in church,
但我们需要证据
but we need proof.
我要求在所有人面前开听证会
I demand a full hearing in front of all of us!
听证会会有的
Oh, you'll get your hearing.
周二下午四点
Tuesday at 4:00.
又失了一个乐园
Another paradise lost.
丽莎  你真的搞砸了大斋期的第一个周日
Lisa, you're really bringing down the first Sunday of Lent.
由大斋首日开始至复活节前日止  一共四十天
连吞火者都不开心了
Even the fire eater is sad.
信仰危机愈发严重
The crisis of faith grows
牧师纵火
禁止其传教的支持率目前高达52%
as support for im-preach-ment is now at 52%.
可以用解雇解决纵火吗
Can you fight fire with firing?
我们该如何处理这位叛徒神父
What should we do with this Judas priest?
肯特·布罗克曼为您报道
This has been Kent Brockman talking,
闭口不谈
saying nothing.
闭口不说不谈
燃烧男子  伯德·莱特案受审
春田市政厅
欢迎各位  我们开始吧
Welcome, all of you. Let's begin.
为什么是她来主持
Why is she running this?
因为她不会激动过头
Because she won't get overexcited.
那我就会吗
And I will?!
而且《圣经》上说  "小孩要牵引他们"
And the Bible said, "A child shall lead them."
出自《以赛亚书11:6》
正如佛祖所说
Well, as my Lord Buddha said,
"此三者不可久藏
"Three things cannot long be hidden.
日  月  真相"
The sun, the moon, and the truth."
他们怎么不把这话设成谷歌涂鸦
Well, why don't they make that a Google Doodle?
神父  你很关心《圣经》
Reverend, you're very concerned with the Bible.
那我们就来谈谈《圣经》
So, let us turn to that Bible.
尤其是那众多
Specifically, the very, very, many parts
谈及宽恕的部分
that speak about forgiveness.
《约翰福音1:9》如果我们坦白罪孽  祂便会宽恕
《希伯来书8:12》我要宽恕其不义  忘怀其罪愆
《提摩太前书1:15·16》基督耶稣降世  为要拯救罪人
《路加福音23:34》耶稣说  父啊  赦免他们  他们不知道自己在做什么
妈  谢谢你缝了这些旗帜
And, Mom, thank you for sewing these banners.
我缝了那么久  你就说十秒吗
I did all that work for a ten-second bit?
他烧过  他承认了
He did it. He admitted it.
你还需要什么证据
What else do you need?
大家  证据更少我们都围攻过
We've mobbed for less, people.
对  还记得那个两只袜子颜色不同的人吗
Yeah, remember the guy with the two different-colored socks?
他从小镇溜走了
Ran his ass right out of town.
驱逐他
Banish him!
驱逐他  驱逐他
Banish him! Banish him!
珍惜他  珍惜他
Cherish him! Cherish him!
我知道还有一个长发表演家
I know another long-haired performer
宣扬着爱与和平的新哲理
who preached a new philosophy, peace and love.
人们一开始是站在他这边的
And the crowd was with him,
后来却完全转变了
but then they turned, hard.
那个人就是威利·纳尔逊
And that man's name was Willie Nelson!
美国著名乡村摇滚音乐人
要我说  驱逐他  驱逐他
Well, I say, banish him! Banish him!
驱逐他  驱逐他
Banish him! Banish him!
好了
Stop!
我是来团结你们的  但我却让你们分裂了
I came here to unify you, but instead I divided you.
所以我打算离开了
So I'm leaving.
我只希望我所说的能与你们少数人产生共鸣
I just hope what I said resonated with a few of you.
比如丽莎  她可能会改变世界
Like Lisa, one who may change the world.
还有那位船长  他清醒得令人吃惊
And that Sea Captain guy. That dude is surprisingly woke.
如果激进主义不插手要它还有何用
Ya, activism means nothing if it's not intersectional. Yarr!
春田镇市政厅
很高兴与你相识
Glad to have known you.
我只想说  你永远改变了我的生活
I just want to say, you've changed my life forever.
你是我遇见的第一个
You're the first minister I've ever met
我不想一巴掌扇过去的牧师
I didn't want to slap across the face.
很高兴与你相识
Glad to have known you.
我只想说  去死吧  圣经焚烧者
And I just want to say, rot in Hell, Bible burner.
很高兴与你相识
Glad to have known you.
-很高兴与...  -打住打住
- Glad to have... - Bup-bup-bup.
在我们家  没有烘肉卷
In my family, you don't say goodbye to someone
你是没法和一个你在乎的人道别的
you care about without a meat loaf.
还有西兰花
And broccoli.
你是在邀请我去吃晚餐吗
You-You're inviting me over for dinner?
如果你在看见我们吃饭后还喜欢我们
If you can love us after seeing us eat,
我们就知道你是真的喜欢我们
we'll know you really love us.
来吧  哥们  我们准备做烤圣经
Come on, pal. We're having roast Bible.
怎么了  玩笑开太早了
What? Too soon?
我想做个简单的祷告
I just want to offer this simple prayer:
亲爱的上帝  请让辛普森一家永不终结
Dear God, please let the Simpsons never end.
阿门
Amen.
还有  伯德  明天我得问你一个哲学问题
And, Bode, tomorrow I have to ask you a philosophical question,
我们在教堂见
so I'll see you at the church.
-阿门  -你刚刚去哪了
- Amen. - Where the hell have you been?
春田第一教堂
陈旧管理模式中
《偶然圣人》《普世基督》《你在天堂中遇到的五个混蛋》
你为什么要烧掉圣经
Why would you burn a Bible?
你怎么不烧本比尔·奥雷利的书呢
Why couldn't you burn Bill O'Reilly's books?
美国记者  作家  政治评论员
他写了那么多书
There are so many.
我是想告诉人们上帝在你们心中
I was trying to tell people that God is in your heart,
而不是在过度建设的教堂或者书本里
not in a overbuilt cathedral or some book.
这座小镇读不懂潜台词
This town doesn't get subtext.
我们的国家公共广播电台直播摔跤
Our NPR station broadcasts wrestling.
这是个很凶残的扼颈招式
And that's an excruciating half nelson.
这就是传说中的"打脸"吗
Now, is that what's known in the lexicon as a "face stomp"?
是的  正是如此
Yes, yes, its.
本周是广播电台募捐周  请捐赠一份善心
This is NPR pledge week. Please give.
-你为什么要那么做  -我那时才19岁
- Why did you do it? - I was 19.
我目睹了人们是如何用圣经分裂和排斥他人
I saw how people were using the Bible to divide and exclude.
人们忙于对路线图顶礼膜拜
People were so busy worshipping a road map
却没有朝目的地努力前行
instead of trying to reach the destination.
你懂我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
你怎么不这么说呢
Well, why didn't you just say that?
这话在理  你也不用烧《圣经》
That was fine. No fire.
-我才19岁  -我现在8岁  我能明白
- I was 19. - I'm eight and I get it.
你说得对  从那天起我就后悔了
You're right. I've regretted it since the day I did it.
所以从那时起  我就在世界各地闲逛
So, since then, I've just wandered the world,
就像一个在间隔年的千禧一代
like a millennial on a gap year.
我明白  但你打算怎么说服...
I understand, but how are you gonna convince...?
大象都震怒了  我们永不原谅
我曾信任过你们  地狱里的新公寓
我就对这小镇的开阔心胸满怀信心吧
I'll just have faith in this town's open heart.
我就确认下上面写的不是"我们原谅你"
I was just making sure it doesn't say "We forgive you."
-不是的  -除非是用红色写的
- It doesn't. - Unless they wrote it in red.
对  不是的
Yeah, no.
-不  不是的  -不是
- No, they didn't. - No.
-这块砖就是信息  -这就是我们镇的人
- The brick is the message. - Them's my people.
-是啊  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我们要扔回去吗  你们的习俗是什么样的
Do we throw it back? What's your custom?
警长  这人的码表上还有十分钟
Uh, Chief, this guy still had ten minutes on his meter.
就在我理解了那人时  在我重新相信时
Just when I understood that guy, when I believed again,
在我信任人们时  他们就把他抓走了
when I believed in people, they took him away.
我失去了我的信仰  阿卢
I've lost my faith, Lou.
没事警长  你有漂亮的妻子和孩子  我没法...
Come on, Chief, you got a beautiful wife and kid-- I can't...
抱歉  我没法一本正经说这话
I'm sorry, I can't say that with a straight face.
你可以试试啊
Well, you could try.
我是  我在试了  抱歉
I am. I-I'm trying, I'm sorry.
抱歉  我再试试
I'm sorry. I'll maybe try again.
你有漂亮的妻子和孩子
You got a beautiful wife and kid.